kiwibank.co.nz 2011-11-06

# Privacy and Security - Kiwibank

## Privacy

In the course of providing you with our accounts and services, we may collect personal information from you. We will collect, hold and use your personal information by in accordance with our privacy policy.

## Security

Information transmitted over the internet is inherently insecure. However, we have physical, electronic and managerial processes in place to protect the information we collect via our website or email. The information you send is passed through a secure server using encryption technology. All stored customer information is protected with secure passwords, user log-ons and other security procedures.

## Intellectual property rights

We hold all copyright and other intellectual property rights in this website. You may use the information on this website and reproduce it (electronically or in hard copy) for your personal use only.

In all other circumstances, you must get written consent from us before you use, send or reproduce any of the information on this website.

## Governing law

This website is governed by New Zealand law. When you access this website, you submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the New Zealand courts.

This website contains applications that collect personal information about you. Kiwibank will collect this personal information so that it can offer you its accounts and services, process your application, carry out credit checks and verify your identity. We will hold this personal information securely and will only use it in developing and running Kiwibank and/or providing you information about accounts and services that we think might be of interest to you (including from our selected business partners). If you ask us not to provide you with this information, we will comply with your request. You may ask us to show you the personal information we hold about you and to make corrections to it.

Kiwibank may record your visit to this website for analysis of website activity (such as the number of users who visit this website, the date and time of visits, the number of pages viewed, navigation patterns, what country and what systems users have used to access the site and, when entering this website from another website, the address of that website). Some of this information will be gathered through the use of "cookies". A cookie is a small text file placed on your computer's hard drive or browser by a webpage server. If you want to disable these cookies, you may do so by changing the setting on your browser. However, if you disable cookies, you may not be able to use all the functions on this website.
